kyaboss.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy & Terms Of Use - KyaBoss

**Kyaboss.com is commited to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private and is used only for the purposes as** **set forth herein.**

**Privacy**

This privacy policy sets out how Kyaboss.com uses and protects any information that you give Kyaboss.com when you use Kyaboss.com. Kyaboss.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using Kyaboss.com, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Kyaboss.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st July 2015.

**Information About All Kyaboss.com Visitors  
**In general we collect data about the areas of the sites and pages that are visited. We only aggregate this data and do not specifically target the trends of an individual. This information helps us to better serve you by determining which services and features are most useful to you. We may share this information with partners, but again this is only in aggregate form and individuals will not be able to be identified from the data.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

We use third party advertising networks to deliver our adverts. These networks may use  **online behavioural advertising**  cookies to enable them to tailor the adverts and to make them more relevant to you. Further information on how these companies manage your information can be found on their websites. The networks we use directly are Google Adsense, Doubleclick, Matomy Media and Taboola.

**The Use & Storage Of Personal Information  
**When you supply any personal information to Kyaboss.com (e.g. newsletter registration) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we handle that data. In general, any information you provide to Kyaboss.com will only be used inside our organisation and by its service providers. It will never be supplied to anyone outside our organisation without your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted to by law.

**Children  
**If you are aged 18 or under, please get your parent/guardian’s permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to Kyaboss.com. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information.

**Security  
**We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Links to other websites  
**Our website contains links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by our privacy policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Kyaboss.com’s relationship with you in relation to this website. The term ‘Kyaboss.com’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is in the British Virgin Islands. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website. The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
  * Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  * All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.
  * Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
  * This website contains links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
  * Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of the United States of America.
